naturepedic.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy

Naturepedic (or the “Company”) values the privacy of its customers and Web/blog site viewers. Any of the following personal information that may be made available to Naturepedic when browsing or navigating the site shall be kept confidential:

  * First and last name
  * Company, home, postal or other physical address
  * Other contact information, for example, telephone number, fax number, email address, and other similar information
  * Any other information needed to provide a service you requested

**Examples of scenarios** where our visitors provide their personal information include, but may not be limited, to:

  * Emailing, calling or communicating with us.
  * Posting a question or comment through the site.
  * Requesting literature.
  * Participating in an online survey.
  * Requesting inclusion in an email or other mailing list.
  * Submitting an entry for a contest or other promotions.
  * Logging in to the site, thus requiring a user name and/or a password.
  * Placing an order.
  * Any other business-related reason.

The Company provides you the opportunity to agree or decline to give your personal information via the Internet. The Company will inform you of the purpose for the collection and does not intend to transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled “Information Sharing and Disclosure” below. If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may transfer that information, within the Company or to a third party service provider as necessary.

**Domain Information Collection**

The Company may collect domain information to enable us to analyze how our visitors use this site. This data enables us to become more familiar with which people visit our site, how often they visit, and what parts of the site they visit most often. The Company uses this information to improve its Web-based offerings. This information is collected automatically and requires no action on your part.

**Use of Cookies and Tracking User Traffic**

Some pages on this site may use “cookies”—small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID to track the pages visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. These files are used for site registration and customization the next time you visit us.

Some parts of the site may also use cookies to track user traffic patterns. The Company does this in order to determine the usefulness of our Web site information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. Please note that cookies cannot read data off of your hard drive. Your Web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Web site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.

We may use third-party advertising companies to collect data and/or serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit http://networkadvertising.org/. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Your personal information is never shared outside the Company without your permission, except under conditions listed below:

  * Consenting to share your information to a third party service provider working on our behalf to serve you.
  * Requiring us to provide you with a product or service.

The Company will also disclose your personal information, if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our sites.

**Internet Security**

The Company strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often and use a combination of letters, numbers and symbols.

**Protecting the Privacy of Children**

Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for our Web site. To protect their privacy, the Company prohibits the solicitation of personal information from these children.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

This site may contain links to other sites. The Company does not share your personal information with those Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The Company reserves the right to change, modify or update this policy at any time without notice. Any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information will be posted on this site.

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please email us at the contact information on the site.
